https://movie-gazette.com/privacy-policy-statement

Movie Gazette
Movie reviews, news and more
Cookie Policy#18963 (no title)About Movie GazetteCurrent competitionsPR InfoTerms And Conditions Of UsePrivacy Policy StatementUKUSAPast competitions.Twitter FeedSearchSearch Results
Privacy Policy Statement
Identity of the web site administrators: Movie Gazette (movie-gazette.com, moviegazette.co.uk and movie-gazette.co.uk) is a web site of Web Gazette LLP. Our postal address is:
Web Gazette LLP
Holiday House
Valley Drive
Ilkley
West Yorkshire
LS29 8PB
United Kingdom
We can be reached via e-mail at Info.
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer’s domain name and e-mail address (where possible).
We collect:-
the domain name and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our Web page
the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board
the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail
the e-mail addresses of those who make postings to our chat areas
aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit
information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.
The information we collect is:-
used to improve the content of our Web page
used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor
used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site
shared with other reputable organizations to help them contact consumers for marketing purposes
not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.
With respect to cookies we use cookies to:-
store visitors preferences
record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart
record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit
alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site
record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site
customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends.
For statistical purposes to track how many individual unique users we have and how often they visit our websites. We collect data listing which of our pages are most frequently visited and by which types of users and from which countries.
We use third parties to collect anonymous user information, sometimes through cookies and web beacons.
Web Gazette LLP and third party advertisers will generate statistical cookies to track advertising impressions and conversions.
Placing cookies on your computer means we can serve you adverts that you might be more interested in, and allows us to control the number of times you see them and measure how effective the ad campaign has been. This helps us to keep the site free of charge. There is further information on this in the Online Behavioural Advertising section of this privacy policy, including how you can opt out of Online Behavioural advertising.
Flash cookies may be used to store user preferences for media player functionality and without them some video content may not render correctly.
By using the site you are agreeing to the use of cookies as described.
If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address, writing to us at the above address, visiting us at https://movie-gazette.com/subscribe.
If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line or directly in relation to any other specific reason that the telephone number was supplied to us.
With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.
Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by visiting us at https://movie-gazette.com/subscribe.
With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.
Please note that the information you enter may be transferred outside the European Economic Area for the purposes of processing by Movie Gazette. Any transfer of personal information outside of the European Economic Area is done in circumstances ensuring that the information is processed only in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the UK’s Data Protection Act.
Home
Monthly Archives
Monthly Archives
Select Month
April 2014  (1)
January 2013  (5)
December 2012  (5)
November 2012  (7)
October 2012  (5)
September 2012  (5)
August 2012  (8)
July 2012  (5)
June 2012  (5)
May 2012  (9)
April 2012  (10)
March 2012  (10)
February 2012  (9)
January 2012  (14)
December 2011  (10)
November 2011  (9)
October 2011  (10)
September 2011  (10)
August 2011  (10)
July 2011  (11)
June 2011  (9)
May 2011  (6)
April 2011  (2)
March 2011  (10)
February 2011  (34)
January 2011  (10)
December 2010  (11)
November 2010  (17)
October 2010  (9)
September 2010  (6)
August 2010  (15)
July 2010  (9)
June 2010  (21)
May 2010  (24)
April 2010  (9)
March 2010  (9)
February 2010  (17)
January 2010  (14)
December 2009  (10)
November 2009  (24)
October 2009  (18)
September 2009  (23)
August 2009  (70)
July 2009  (19)
June 2009  (218)
April 2009  (87)
March 2009  (39)
February 2009  (94)
January 2009  (113)
December 2008  (3)
October 2007  (40)
September 2007  (47)
April 2007  (4)
February 2007  (19)
September 2006  (20)
August 2006  (44)
September 2005  (7)
August 2005  (79)
July 2005  (212)
June 2005  (451)
May 2005  (445)
April 2005  (469)
March 2005  (491)
February 2005  (375)
January 2005  (312)
December 2004  (312)
November 2004  (426)
October 2004  (537)
September 2004  (131)
August 2004  (401)
July 2004  (414)
June 2004  (58)
May 2004  (32)
April 2004  (20)
March 2004  (30)
February 2004  (1492)
January 2004  (314)
December 2003  (328)
November 2003  (408)
October 2003  (374)
September 2003  (298)
August 2003  (428)
July 2003  (718)
June 2003  (362)
May 2003  (839)
April 2003  (177)
March 2003  (85)
February 2003  (133)
January 2003  (347)
Categories
Competitions (1)
News (1)
Out Now (16)
People (10,928)
Reviews (1,859)
Action (501)
Adventure (272)
Animated (94)
Asian (99)
British (312)
Comedy (681)
Crime (320)
Documentary (47)
Drama (908)
European (252)
Family (187)
Fantasy (210)
Film Of The Book (1)
Horror (272)
Movies (256)
Musical (62)
Mystery (157)
Romance (305)
Science Fiction (230)
Thriller (541)
TV (10)
War (86)
Westerns (27)
Search
Recent Posts
Divergent
Django Unchained
Captain Corelli’s Mandolin
Les Misérables
Quartet
Recent Comments
Home | About Movie Gazette | For Film PR People |Terms Of Use Of This Web Site | Privacy Policy©
Web Gazette LLP | Posters and other images are ©,® of their respective studios.
30 queries in 0.342
seconds.
We use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners. detailsNo problem
